ad-rag.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | adland.tv

This privacy policy sets out how **Adland** uses and protects any information that you give **Adland** when you use this website.

**Adland** is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Since I was never a scout I can't say scouts honor, but how about I swear on my 1964 Vespa Primavera? Love that thing you know.

**Adland** may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. If you're total paranoid control freak or just generally aware of stuff-that-affects you, you should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 2000-02-23.

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:

* name and job title  

* contact information including email address  

* demographic information such as location, preferences and interests 
* other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers / your profile as seen by other adgrunts. 

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

* If you lose your password and need to request a new one, we'll email it to you 
* Internal record keeping.  

* We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
* We may periodically send emails about new features or terms of service changes using the email address which you have provided. 

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. In other words the data is behind napalm-resistant firewalls, and the machines are hidden away in Blofeld's old lair. Ninjas can't even get to our server.

**How we use cookies**  
In nerdspeak, a cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or simply keeps tracks of your personal preferences on the site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes because we think graphs are cool, and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. Cookies are the best when they are chocolate chip.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. You can't log in without cookies, which ruins the fun.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. While links are cool, it doesn't mean we've looked that close at all those sites, much less checked them out periodically to see what's going on. So don't blame us if some site you wander off to is bad or has stuff on it that offends you or your pets. Go ahead and surf the links, but remember, it's at your own risk.. Mmmm'K? (If you meet a very bad website out there which we have linked to, expecting something else, you can always let us know and we'll reconsider that linking.)

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

When setting your profile preferences, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want comments to posts emailed to you. Some people like following conversation this way, some don't - the choice is yours.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties as we hate spammers more than you do. Really we do. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information or news about _this website_ but this is rarer than palladium.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to hostmaster -at- adland.tv.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please correct it in your profile page. If you can not do that, then email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
